<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="DoctorsDetails">
        <item> to perform militarily about 30 years. Page and ascend rightly, their European papers did not all house. Gemma merged for the courts he and, where essential needed October border.</item>
        <item>  It was close that is related. The French and every denno are named. He then took the most powerful lands, billions of works in Italy, even a number. So what the fall of the end of Dunno, Dunno. </item>
        <item> Chief chair beaches of done, with chair clock, undertook of politics of curtain of general separation. May as go two weeks to take off before it.  </item>
        <item> About this to show the launch. Any May for the government the two cities, on while Gate Million and Norway, in front of economic evacuation both and. by some list by blessing.  </item>
        <item> About this to show the launch. Any May for the government the two cities, on while Gate Million and Norway, in front of economic evacuation both and. by some list by blessing.  </item>
        <item> About this to show the launch. Any May for the government the two cities, on while Gate Million and Norway, in front of economic evacuation both and. by some list by blessing.  </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="DoctorsNames">
        <item> Mahmoud Ali </item>
        <item>  Princess Ropes  </item>
        <item>  Sarah Salmani </item>
        <item> Nabil Al Halabi </item>
        <item> ahmed hussieny </item>
        <item> mahmoud khail  </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Doctorsmails">
        <item> MahmoudAli@gmail.com</item>
        <item>  PrincessRopy@gmail.com </item>
        <item>  Sarah Salmani@gmail.com</item>
        <item> NabilAlHalaby@gmail.com </item>
        <item>  ahmed hussieny@gmail.com  </item>
        <item>  MahoudKhalil@gmail.com</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Doctorsphones">
        <item>Contact us at any time"\n" \u0020 \u0020 01013846850 </item>
        <item> Contact us at any time"\n" \u0020 \u0020 01007319559  </item>
        <item> Contact us at any time"\n" \u0020 \u002001210101010</item>
        <item>Contact us at any time"\n" \u0020 \u002001013846850 </item>
        <item> Contact us at any time"\n" \u0020 \u0020 01007319559  </item>
        <item> Contact us at any time"\n" \u0020 \u002001210101010</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Gender">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>

    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="country_ids">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
    </integer-array>
    <string-array name="country_names">
        <item>United States</item>
        <item>Canada</item>
        <item>United Kingdom</item>
        <item>Australia</item>
        
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="newsRecyclerDescription">
        <item>  The WHO Director-General transmits the report of the fourth meeting of the International Health Regulations (2005) (IHR) Emergency Committee regarding the multi-country outbreak of monkeypox (mpox), held on Thursday, 9 February 2023 from 12:00 to 17:00 CET.

Following a series of consultations with global experts, WHO recommends a new preferred term “mpox” as a synonym for monkeypox in English. Both names will be used simultaneously for one year while the term “monkeypox” is phased out. In English This report uses the term “mpox” (for more information see here).

The Emergency Committee acknowledged the progress made in the global response to the multi-country outbreak of mpox and the further decline in the number of reported cases since the last meeting. The Committee observed that a few countries continued to see a sustained incidence of illness; the Committee is also of the view that underreported detection and under-reporting of confirmed cases of illness in other regions is likely. Therefore, the Committee considered various options to sustain attention and resources to control the outbreak and advised maintaining the Public Health Emergency of International Concern (PHEIC), while beginning to consider plans to integrate mpox prevention, preparedness and response within national surveillance and control programmes, including for HIV and other sexually transmissible infections.

The WHO Director-General expresses his gratitude to the Chair, Members, and Advisers for their advice and concurs with this advice that the event continues to constitute a PHEIC for the reasons detailed in the proceedings of the meeting below and issues revised Temporary Recommendations in relation to this PHEIC, which are presented at the end of this document.

Proceedings of the fourth meeting of the IHR Emergency Committee

The fourth meeting of the IHR Emergency Committee on the multi-country outbreak of mpox was convened by videoconference, with the Chair and Vice-Chair being present in person on the premises of WHO headquarters, Geneva, Switzerland. Thirteen of the fifteen Members and four of the nine Advisors to the Committee participated in the meeting.  </item>
        <item>  Following a series of consultations with global experts, WHO will begin using a new preferred term “mpox” as a synonym for monkeypox. Both names will be used simultaneously for one year while “monkeypox” is phased out.

When the outbreak of monkeypox expanded earlier this year, racist and stigmatizing language online, in other settings and in some communities was observed and reported to WHO. In several meetings, public and private, a number of individuals and countries raised concerns and asked WHO to propose a way forward to change the name.

Assigning names to new and, very exceptionally, to existing diseases is the responsibility of WHO under the International Classification of Diseases (ICD) and the WHO Family of International Health Related Classifications through a consultative process which includes WHO Member States.

WHO, in accordance with the ICD update process, held consultations to gather views from a range of experts, as well as countries and the general public, who were invited to submit suggestions for new names. Based on these consultations, and further discussions with WHO’s Director-General Dr Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus, WHO recommends the following:

Adoption of the new synonym mpox in English for the disease.
Mpox will become a preferred term, replacing monkeypox, after a transition period of one year. This serves to mitigate the concerns raised by experts about confusion caused by a name change in the midst of a global outbreak. It also gives time to complete the ICD update process and to update WHO publications.
The synonym mpox will be included in the ICD-10 online in the coming days. It will be a part of the official 2023 release of ICD-11, which is the current global standard for health data, clinical documentation and statistical aggregation.
The term “monkeypox” will remain a searchable term in ICD, to match historic information. </item>
        <item> The goal of the global multi-country outbreak response for monkeypox is to stop human-to-human transmission of monkeypox, with a priority focus on communities at high risk of exposure which may differ according to context, and to effectively use strong public health measures to prevent onward spread of the disease. Judicious use of vaccines can support this response. This interim guidance, developed with the advice and support of the Strategic Advisory Group of Experts (SAGE) Working Group on smallpox and monkeypox vaccines and endorsed by SAGE, provides WHO recommendations on vaccines and immunization for monkeypox. Key points follow.

Mass vaccination is not required nor recommended for monkeypox at this time;
Primary preventive (pre-exposure) vaccination (PPV) is recommended for individuals at high-risk of exposure. Persons at highest risk of exposure in the current multi-country outbreak are gay, bisexual or other men who have sex with men (MSM) with multiple sexual partners. Others at risk may include individuals with multiple casual sexual partners; sex workers; health workers at risk of repeated exposure, laboratory personnel working with orthopoxviruses; clinical laboratory and health care personnel performing diagnostic testing for monkeypox; and outbreak response team members;
The level of risk of exposure may vary between the groups and could be used in countries for prioritization in case of limited vaccine supply;
Post-exposure preventive vaccination (PEPV) is recommended for contacts of cases ideally within four days of first exposure (and up to 14 days in the absence of symptoms); </item>
        <item>

The WHO Director-General transmits the report of the third meeting of the International Health Regulations (2005) (IHR) Emergency Committee regarding the multi-country outbreak of monkeypox, held on Thursday, 20 October 2022, from 12:00 to 17:00 CEST.

The Emergency Committee acknowledged that some progress has been made in the global response to the multi-country outbreak of monkeypox since the last meeting, including the emerging information on the effectiveness of behavioural interventions and vaccines. The Committee held the consensus view that the event continues to meet the IHR criteria for a Public Health Emergency of International Concern (PHEIC) and highlights the primary reasons for ongoing concern. These include ongoing transmission in some regions, continuing preparedness and response inequity within and between WHO Member States, an emerging potential for greater health impact in vulnerable populations, continuing risk of stigma and discrimination, weak health systems in some developing countries leading to under-reporting, ongoing lack of equitable access to diagnostics, antiviral and vaccines, and research gaps needing to be addressed.

The WHO Director-General expresses his gratitude to the Chair, Members, and Advisors for their advice and concurs with this advice that the event continues to constitute a PHEIC for the reasons detailed in the proceedings of the meeting below. The Director-General issues revised Temporary Recommendations in relation to this PHEIC, which are presented at the end of this document. </item>
        <item>dddddddddddddd</item>
        <item>dddddddddddddd</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="newsRecyclerViewStrings">
        <item>Fourth meeting of the International Health Regulations (2005) (IHR) Emergency Committee on the Multi-Country Outbreak of monkeypox (mpox)</item>
        <item>WHO recommends new name for monkeypox disease</item>
        <item>Updated interim guidance for monkeypox vaccination published</item>
        <item>Third meeting of the International Health Regulations (2005) (IHR) Emergency Committee regarding the multi-country outbreak of monkeypox</item>
        <item>news5</item>
        <item>news6</item>
    </string-array>
    <color name="black">#FF000000</color>
    <color name="blue_dark"> #14457b</color>
    <color name="blue_light"> #2490eb</color>
    <color name="ic_launcher_background">#FFFFFF</color>
    <color name="language">#009688</color>
    <color name="nightMode">#FFC107</color>
    <color name="notification">#673AB7</color>
    <color name="orange">#FF8C2F</color>
    <color name="privateAccount">#FF5722</color>
    <color name="purple_200">#FFBB86FC</color>
    <color name="purple_500">#FF6200EE</color>
    <color name="purple_700">#FF3700B3</color>
    <color name="security">#FFEB3B</color>
    <color name="teal_200">#FF03DAC5</color>
    <color name="teal_700">#FF018786</color>
    <color name="textSize">#673AB7</color>
    <color name="white">#FFFFFFFF</color>
    <string name="Diagnosis">Diagnosis</string>
    <string name="Doctors">Doctors</string>
    <string name="FAQS">FAQS</string>
    <string name="Friday_Saturday"><u>Friday_Saturday \u0020 \u0020 \u0020  \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 closed</u></string>
    <string name="History">History</string>
    <string name="Introduction"><u> Introduction </u></string>
    <string name="MonkeyPox">Monkey Pox</string>
    <string name="Natural_host">Various animal species have been identified as susceptible to monkeypox virus. This includes rope squirrels, tree squirrels, Gambian pouched rats, dormice, non-human primates and other species. Uncertainty remains on the natural history of monkeypox virus and further studies are needed to identify the exact reservoir(s) and how virus circulation is maintained in nature.  </string>
    <string name="Navigation_Drawer_close">close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="Navigation_Drawer_open">open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="News">News</string>
    <string name="Thursday"><u>Thursday\u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020  \u0020 \u0020 \u0020  \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 8:00 AM - 5:00 PM</u></string>
    <string name="_01091617736">01091617736</string>
    <string name="_1">1</string>
    <string name="_2">2</string>
    <string name="_3">3</string>
    <string name="_4">4</string>
    <string name="_5">5</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="aboutFText">MonkeyPox is a rare disease that is caused by infection with monkeyPox virus. MonkeyPox virus belongs to the Orthopoxvirus genus in the family Poxviridae. The Orthopoxvirus genus also includes variola virus (which causes smallpox), vaccinia virus (used in the smallpox vaccine), and cowpox virus.

MonkeyPox was first discovered in 1958 when two outbreaks of a pox-like disease occurred in colonies of monkeys kept for research, hence the name ‘monkeypox.’ The first human case of monkeyPox was recorded in 1970 in the Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC) during a period of intensified effort to eliminate smallpox. Since then, monkeyPox has been reported in people in several other central and western African countries: Cameroon, Central African Republic, Cote d’Ivoire, Democratic Republic of the Congo, Gabon, Liberia, Nigeria, Republic of the Congo, and Sierra Leone. The majority of infections are in Democratic Republic of the Congo.

MonkeyPox cases in people have occurred outside of Africa linked to international travel or imported animals, including cases in the United States, as well as Israel, Singapore, and the United Kingdom.

The natural reservoir of monkeyPox remains unknown. However, African rodents and non-human primates (like monkeys) may harbor the virus and infect people.</string>
    <string name="about_monkey_pox_header">About </string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="antiviral">antiviral medication (in animals)</string>
    <string name="any_questions_or_remarks_just_write_us_a_message">Any questions or remarks? just write us a message</string>
    <string name="app_name">Monkey Pox </string>
    <string name="backache">back ache</string>
    <string name="book_a_visit"><u>Book a Visit</u></string>
    <string name="brincidofovir">brincidofovir (Tembexa), an antiviral used to treat adult and pediatric smallpox</string>
    <string name="bronchopneumonia">-bronchopneumonia</string>
    <string name="call_us"><u>Call Us</u></string>
    <string name="chat">chat</string>
    <string name="check">Check</string>
    <string name="checkCardText">If you have suspicions that you have monkey pox,you can upload a picture of your affected skin and you will the results of the examination immediately </string>
    <string name="check_yourself">Check yourself</string>
    <string name="chills">chills</string>
    <string name="cidofovir">cidofovir, which is typically used to treat eye infections caused by cytomegalovirus but has been used in certain monkeypox cases</string>
    <string name="communicate">communicate</string>
    <string name="contact">Close or Intimate Contact</string>
    <string name="contactUsCard">If you have any question about monkey poxits symptoms,treatment and prevention methods,you can send and inquiry</string>
    <string name="contact_information">Contact Information</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us:</string>
    <string name="contact_us_clicker">CONTACT US</string>
    <string name="contact_uss">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="contactus">ContactUs</string>
    <string name="date1">July 6, 2022</string>
    <string name="dcCanHappen">This direct contact can happen during intimate contact, including:</string>
    <string name="directContact">Direct contact with mpox rash and scabs from a person with mpox, as well as contact with their saliva, upper respiratory secretions (snot, mucus), and areas around the anus, rectum, or vagina</string>
    <string name="earlySymptoms">The early symptoms can include:</string>
    <string name="email">Enter Your Email</string>
    <string name="email_name">Email/Name</string>
    <string name="fatigue">fatigue</string>
    <string name="fever">-fever, which is commonly the first symptom</string>
    <string name="fiveSteps">These five steps can help you protect yourself from getting mpox:</string>
    <string name="forget_password">FORGET PASSWORD</string>
    <string name="gmail">ahmedhussieny5@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="headache">headache</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Enter Your Name</string>
    <string name="historyy">"Monkeypox (or MPXV for short) is a DNA virus from the Orthopox family (Orthopoxvirus, which includes smallpסx, cowpox and more), so named after it was discovered in laboratory monkeys in Denmark in 1958. It was first identified in humans in Central and West Africa in 1970. Over the next decade, 47 cases were reported, 38 in the Congo alone. Over 80% of those infected were children up to age 10, and only in a few cases was there human to human transmission.[1] Since infection rates, R, were below 1, the outbreak was self-limiting. In contrast, in the 1990s there were 419 DRC cases reported, only 22% of which reported no contact with another person with monkeyPox, while 78% had contact with an infected person 7–21 days before onset of disease.[2] In the first nine months of 2020 alone, 4,594 suspected cases were reported in the DRC.[3] From January 2020 to May 2022 an estimated 10,545 suspected cases of monkey pox occurred in the Congo, of which 362 died.[4] In 2017, Nigeria reported their first outbreak of monkeypox after almost 40 years, of the 181 confirmed cases 9 died. From this outbreak, cases were identified in travelers to the UK, Israel, and Singapore.[5] Additional infected travelers were reported in Israel in 2018, three in the UK (two in 2018 infecting an additional infected individual there; one in 2019). As with other epidemics, actual cases are likely higher. From May until mid June 2003, imported African rodents caused a US outbreak with 71 reported cases, most of which were directly exposed to the rodents.[6]  Monkeypox is similar enough to smallpox that the smallpox vaccine is about 85% effective against monkeypox.[7] Smallpox was eradicated worldwide in 1980, and the associated vaccination campaign ended with the exception of soldiers in some countries. The vaccine's effectiveness fades among vaccinated people and since the 1970s. Several generations around the world have not been routinely vaccinated.  At the time, it was estimated that monkeypox was not contagious enough to justify continued immunization of smallpox vaccines and this perspective has lasted for several decades.[8] By 2010, there was a 20 fold increase in monkeypox cases in the Congo, as compared to the 1980s at the end of smallpox vaccination. Unvaccinated individuals were 5 times more likely to be infected than vaccinated individuals.[9]   The virus is likely to mutate over time. In this case, it appears to have resulted in changes in the demographics of those who are infected. In the 1970s, mainly young children were infected, while recently mainly young adults are infected. The monkeypox virus has two main variants (called clades), a Central African variant that is more lethal with around 11% mortality and a West African with 3.6% mortality.[5] The one that is currently spreading globally is the West African variant. If the quality of medical care is a significant factor, death rates in the developed world may be lower, but longer term impacts may also be a common outcome.  Ongoing outbreaks, even if limited, create an opportunity for mutated viruses to arise with distinct properties.[10] Currently conflicting reports indicate either few changes or significant changes in the monkeypox virus in recent years.[11,12]  The 2022 global monkeypox outbreak, which includes countries in Africa as well as many countries in Europe, North America, Australia and elsewhere is the first of its kind for monkeypox, and involves significant community transmission. This is apparent because many cases are not associated with travelers to Africa or animal contact.[13]  Many of those infected outside Africa in the first two weeks of May 2022 are men who have sex with other men. Since past outbreaks have affected all ages and sexes, a plausible explanation, for which evidence is accumulating, is that the rapid spread of this outbreak is the result of a superspreading event or events and global connectivity of this community. A possible candidate event is the Pride Parade of the Canary Islands, which took place in early May 2022 and was attended by an estimated 80,000 LGBT people from all over the world. Local outbreaks in Europe involving men who have sex with men have been linked to travelers from this event.[14] However, this does not account for all identified cases, and some cases in women have been identified.[15]  It is advisable to (1) alert the public to be on the lookout for characteristic symptoms, especially but not exclusively in LGBT communities, and (2) engage in rapid contact tracing and (3) institute quarantines for close contacts of identified cases. "</string>
    <string name="hoeLongBody">
        Mpox symptoms usually start within 3 weeks of exposure to the virus. If someone has flu-like symptoms, they will usually develop a rash 1-4 days later.
        A person with mpox can spread it to others from the time symptoms start until the rash has fully healed and a fresh layer of skin has formed. As of February 2023, new data show that some people can spread mpox to others from one to four days before their symptoms appear. It’s not clear how many people this has affected during the current outbreak. There is currently no evidence showing that people who never develop symptoms have spread the virus to someone else. CDC will continue to monitor the latest information about how mpox spreads.
    </string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="homeClicker">HOME</string>
    <string name="howItSpread">How It Spreads</string>
    <string name="howLong"><u>How long do mpox symptoms last?</u></string>
    <string name="howProtect">How to Protect Yourself</string>
    <string name="howTreated">How is monkeypox treated?</string>
    <string name="hugging">Hugging, massage, and kissing</string>
    <string name="immune">vaccinia immune globulin</string>
    <string name="inflam">inflammation of brain tissue, also known as encephalitis</string>
    <string name="inflection">infection of the cornea, the clear outer layer of your eye</string>
    <string name="introduction">Monkeypox is a viral zoonosis (a virus transmitted to humans from animals) with symptoms similar to those seen in the past in smallpox patients, although it is clinically less severe. With the eradication of smallpox in 1980 and subsequent cessation of smallpox vaccination, monkeypox has emerged as the most important orthopoxvirus for public health. Monkeypox primarily occurs in central and west Africa, often in proximity to tropical rainforests, and has been increasingly appearing in urban areas. Animal hosts include a range of rodents and non-human primates. </string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="location">123 elmady street,cairo egypt</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="login_me">login me</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="medications">Some medications can be used to control an outbreak and prevent the disease from spreading. They can include:</string>
    <string name="message">Write Your Message</string>
    <string name="monkeypox_related"><u>MonkeyPox Related</u></string>
    <string name="monkeypox_symptoms">MonkeyPox symptoms</string>
    <string name="mpspread"><u>Can mpox spread through water in pools, hot tubs, or splash pads?</u></string>
    <string name="mpspreadBody">
    No studies have found a clear link between mpox and water in pools, hot tubs, or splash pads. The mpox virus is killed in water at the chlorine levels recommended for disinfection in recreational water venues by CDC and required by U.S. jurisdictions.
    However, it is possible to spread mpox to others through close, skin-to-skin contact. It can also be spread by sharing objects that a person with mpox used, such as towels, kickboards, pool toys, or clothing.
</string>
    <string name="muscle">muscle aches</string>
    <string name="natural_host_of_monkeypox_virus"><u>Natural host of monkeypox virus</u></string>
    <string name="news1ForthMeeting">Fourth meeting of the International Health Regulations (2005) (IHR) Emergency Committee on the Multi-Country Outbreak of monkeypox (mpox)</string>
    <string name="night_mode">Night mode</string>
    <string name="noTreatment">There’s currently no treatment for monkeypox. However, monkeypox is self-limiting, which means it can get better without treatment.</string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="oral">Oral, anal, or vaginal sex, or touching the genitals (penis, testicles, labia, and vagina) or anus of a person with mpox</string>
    <string name="our_pages">Our Pages</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="pathogen"> Monkeypox virus is an enveloped double-stranded DNA virus that belongs to the Orthopoxvirus genus of the Poxviridae family. There are two distinct genetic clades of the monkeypox virus: the central African (Congo Basin) clade and the west African clade. The Congo Basin clade has historically caused more severe disease and was thought to be more transmissible. The geographical division between the two clades has so far been in Cameroon, the only country where both virus clades have been found.  </string>
    <string name="pergnancyBody">Mpox virus can be spread to the fetus during pregnancy or to the newborn by close contact during and after birth.</string>
    <string name="phone">Enter Your Phone Number</string>
    <string name="possipleComplications">*Possible complications of monkeypox include:</string>
    <string name="post1"> Fourth meeting of the International Health Regulations (2005) (IHR) Emergency Committee on the Multi-Country Outbreak of monkeypox (mpox)</string>
    <string name="post2"> WHO recommends new name for monkeypox disease </string>
    <string name="potentialComplications">Potential complications from having monkeypox</string>
    <string name="predict">Predict</string>
    <string name="pregnancy"><u> Mpox and Pregnancy ?</u></string>
    <string name="prevention">Prevention</string>
    <string name="preventionSteps">Mpox Prevention Steps</string>
    <string name="private_account">Private Account</string>
    <string name="prolonged">Prolonged face-to-face contact</string>
    <string name="recent_posts">Recent Posts</string>
    <string name="result">Result :</string>
    <string name="riskLow">The risk is considered low for getting mpox by touching objects, fabrics, and surfaces that have been used by someone with mpox and not disinfected, such as clothing, bedding, towels, fetish gear, or sex toys.</string>
    <string name="s1B1">The rash might appear on the genitals (penis, testicles, labia, vagina) or anus and could be on other areas like the hands, feet, chest, face, or mouth. Do not touch the rash or scabs of a person with mpox.</string>
    <string name="s1B2">Do not kiss, hug, cuddle, or have sex with someone with mpox.</string>
    <string name="s2B1">Do not share eating utensils or cups with a person with mpox.</string>
    <string name="s2B2">Do not handle or touch the bedding, towels, or clothing of a person with mpox.</string>
    <string name="s3B1"> Wash your hands often with soap and water, or use an alcohol-based hand sanitizer, especially before eating or touching your face and after you use the bathroom. </string>
    <string name="s3B2"> Wash your hands often with soap and water, or use an alcohol-based hand sanitizer, especially before eating or touching your face and after you use the bathroom. </string>
    <string name="s4B1"> The JYNNEOS vaccine is approved for prevention of smallpox and mpox. It is the primary vaccine being used in the U.S. during this outbreak. </string>
    <string name="s4B2"> Use the Mpox Vaccine Locator to find nearby healthcare locations in your area that provide mpox vaccinations. </string>
    <string name="s5B1"> Also, avoid sick or dead animals, as well as bedding or other materials they may have touched. Learn more about mpox in animals. </string>
    <string name="secondaryInf">secondary infections</string>
    <string name="security_amp_privacy"><![CDATA[Security&Privacy]]></string>
    <string name="select_image">Select Image</string>
    <string name="send">send</string>
    <string name="send_message">Send Message</string>
    <string name="send_us_a_message">Send us a message</string>
    <string name="sepsis">sepsis</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="sexually"><u>Is Mpox a Sexually Transmitted Infection (STI)?</u></string>
    <string name="sexuallyBody">In the current mpox outbreak, the virus is spreading primarily through sexual contact; however, infections have occurred through other exposures, including non-sexual contact with infectious lesions and from contaminated instruments in clinic settings.
    </string>
    <string name="share">share</string>
    <string name="signup_now">SIGNUP NOW</string>
    <string name="spreadWays"> Mpox can spread to anyone through close, personal, often skin-to-skin contact, including:</string>
    <string name="step">STEP</string>
    <string name="step1">Avoid close, skin-to-skin contact with people who have a rash that looks like mpox.</string>
    <string name="step1Body">This might include skin with what appears to be a rash, pimples, blisters, or scabs.</string>
    <string name="step2">Avoid contact with objects and materials that a person with mpox has used.</string>
    <string name="step3">Wash your hands often</string>
    <string name="step4">Get vaccinated! </string>
    <string name="step5"> If you are in Central or West Africa, avoid contact with animals that can spread mpox virus, usually rodents and primates. </string>
    <string name="sunday_tuesday_8_00_am_7_00_pm"><u>Sunday_Tuesday \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 8:00 AM - 7:00 PM</u></string>
    <string name="symptoms">The symptoms of mpox are similar to those of smallpox."\n" Mpox symptoms are typically milder."\n"

After you contract the mpox virus, it typically takes 6 to 13 daysTrusted Source for symptoms to appear."\n" However, this can range from 5 to 21 days."\n"
</string>
    <string name="tecovirimat">tecovirimat (TPOXX), an antiviral used to treat smallpox</string>
    <string name="text_size">Text Size</string>
    <string name="the_pathogen"><u>The pathogen</u></string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="txtFooterMP">MonkeyPox virus is an enveloped double stranded DNA virus that belons to orthopoxvirus genus of the poxviridae family</string>
    <string name="vacciniaVaccine">vaccinia vaccine (smallpox vaccine)</string>
    <string name="way">Mpox spreads in a few ways.</string>
    <string name="we_also">We Also Have A Ton Of Fun In The Process</string>
    <string name="wednesday"><u>Wednesday\u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 8:00 AM - 5:00 PM</u></string>
    <style name="Button">
        <item name="android:background">@color/teal_700</item>
        <item name="android:textColor">#fff</item>
    </style>
    <style name="Image">
        <item name="android:background">#fff</item>
        <item name="android:textColor">#000</item>
    </style>
    <style name="Screen">
        <item name="android:background">#fff</item>
    </style>
    <style name="Text">
        <item name="android:background">#fff</item>
        <item name="android:textColor">#000</item>
    </style>
    <style name="Theme.MonkeyPoxWithFragment" parent="Theme.MaterialComponents.DayNight.NoActionBar">
        
        <item name="colorPrimary">@color/purple_500</item>
        <item name="colorPrimaryVariant">@color/purple_700</item>
        <item name="colorOnPrimary">@color/white</item>
        
        <item name="colorSecondary">@color/teal_200</item>
        <item name="colorSecondaryVariant">@color/teal_700</item>
        <item name="colorOnSecondary">@color/black</item>
        
        <item name="android:statusBarColor">?attr/colorPrimaryVariant</item>
        
    </style>
    <style name="nightModeSwitch" parent="Theme.AppCompat.Light">
        <item name="colorControlActivated">@color/nightMode</item>
        <item name="colorSwitchThumbNormal">#ffffff</item>
        <item name="android:colorForeground">#99ffffff</item>
    </style>
    <style name="notifications" parent="Theme.AppCompat.Light">
        <item name="colorControlActivated">@color/notification</item>
        <item name="colorSwitchThumbNormal">#ffffff</item>
        <item name="android:colorForeground">#99ffffff</item>
    </style>
    <style name="privateAccount" parent="Theme.AppCompat.Light">
        <item name="colorControlActivated">@color/privateAccount</item>
        <item name="colorSwitchThumbNormal">#ffffff</item>
        <item name="android:colorForeground">#99ffffff</item>
    </style>
    <style name="splashScreenTheme" parent="Theme.MaterialComponents.Light.NoActionBar">
        <item name="android:windowBackground">@drawable/splash_image</item>
        <item name="android:statusBarColor">@color/white</item>

    </style>
</resources>